<Publish>
	<!--Id must be set in order to update existed mod. it is not required for publishing mod for the first time-->
	<ModId Value="" />
	<!--Name of the mod to display to players-->
	<DisplayName Value="Skyplan [BETA]" />
	<!--Short description of the mod-->
	<ShortDescription Value="In-game SVG drawing overlay for road, zone, and transit planning before you build." />
	<!--Long description of the mod. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<LongDescription>
## Skyplan

Tracing paper over your city — inside CS2.

Open the overlay with **Alt+P** (rebindable), sketch out your road network, zoning, and transit lines on top of the live map, then build with confidence.

Left-Click to start drawing, Right-Click to end the drawing. For lines, left-click starts a new segment from the end of the previous one. For polygons, left-click adds a point and right-click closes the shape.

### Disclaimer

This is a rough beta version, a lot of the feedback that i got on reddit is not yet implemented. even the Thumbnail is under development.

There is no auto-save nor auto load. please export the plans before closing the game.

The second beta version (milestone) will include:

v0.1.0: Drawing Polish

Make the drawing experience smoother and the overlay easier to use while building.
- Per-layer opacity control
- Global overlay opacity slider
- Layer visibility toggle
- Redo support
- Fuzzy search for layers in the toolbar


### Features
- Line, polygon, and point drawing tools: plan roads, mark zones, drop points of interest
- 24 built-in layers: Transit (Train, Subway, Tram, Bus), Roads (Highway to Local), Zones (Residential, Commercial, Industrial, Office), Public Services, and Points of Interest — each with its own colour and style
- Fully customisable layers: edit `layers.json` to add, remove, or restyle any layer. Changes hot-swap without a game restart
- World-space coordinates: shapes stay pinned to the map as you pan and zoom
- SVG export and import: save your plans as standard SVG files, open them in Inkscape, share them, or import them back later
- Erase tool: with hover highlight
- Undo: (Ctrl+Z)
- Draggable toolbar

## Known Issues
- changing the styles in `layer.json` while already having shapes in the current session wont hot reload. it needs clear-all for the new style to take effect.

## Limitations
- No redo, only undo (Ctrl+Z) is supported.
- No snapping, lines do not snap to roads, the grid, or other shapes.
- Each line is a separate two-point segment, continuous polylines are planned but not yet implemented.
- No layer visibility toggle, individual layers cannot be hidden without clearing them.
- No labeling: there is no way to label the shapes and write custom text. Planned


### Usage

Load a city, press **Alt+P**, draw.
	</LongDescription>
	<Thumbnail Value="Properties/Thumbnail.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/cover.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/line_tool.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/polygon_tool.png" />
	<Screenshot Value="Properties/screenshots/settings_1.png" />
	<!--Tag, can be set multiple times-->
	<Tag Value="Code Mod" />
	<!--Link to the forum post where the mod can be discussed-->
	<ForumLink Value="" />
	<!--Version of the mod-->
	<ModVersion Value="0.0.2-beta" />
	<!--Recommended version of the base game to use the mod-->
	<GameVersion Value="1.6.*" />
	<!--Dependency for the mod, can be set multiple times-->
	<Dependency Id="" />
	<!--Required DLC, can be set multiple times. Supported values are "Landmark Buildings", "San Fransisco Set", "Beach Properties", "Urban Promenades", "Modern Architecture"-->
	<RequiredDLC Value="" />
	<!--Change log for new version. Single line or multi line. Supports minimal markdown subset-->
	<ChangeLog>
## 0.0.2-beta
- Fixed: last shape stays visible after clearing all drawings
- Fixed: keybinding conflict — default key changed from P to Alt+P
- Added: Clear All button (clears all layers at once, undoable with Ctrl+Z)
	</ChangeLog>
	<!--External link, can be set multiple times. supported types are "discord", "github", "youtube", "twitch", "x", "paypal", "patreon", "buymeacoffee", "kofi", "crowdin", "gitlab", "gofundme"-->
	<ExternalLink Type="github" Url="https://github.com/aous-afk/skyplan" />
	<!--Supported values Public, Private, Unlisted-->
	<AccessLevel Value="Private" />
</Publish>
